export const chapter = "Chapter - 11: WATER ";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "What are some activities for which water is essential, according to the text?",
          optionA: "Playing sports",
          optionB: "Cooking food, washing clothes, and taking a bath",
          optionC: "Reading books",
          correctAnswer: "Cooking food, washing clothes, and taking a bath",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is NOT mentioned as a source of water in the text?",
          optionA: "River",
          optionB: "Pond",
          optionC: "Mountain",
          correctAnswer: "Mountain",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Where does rainwater primarily come from, according to the text?",
          optionA: "Underground springs",
          optionB: "Volcanic eruptions",
          optionC: "Rain",
          correctAnswer: "Rain",
        },
        {
          question:
            "How is rainwater collected under the ground, as mentioned in the text?",
          optionA: "Through pipes",
          optionB: "Through wells and hand pumps",
          optionC: "Through solar panels",
          correctAnswer: "Through wells and hand pumps",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is emphasized as a requirement for drinking water in the text?",
          optionA: "It should be hot",
          optionB: "It should be cold",
          optionC: "It should be clean and pure",
          correctAnswer: "It should be clean and pure",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What may happen if we drink dirty water, according to the text?",
          optionA: "We may become superheroes",
          optionB: "We may fall sick badly",
          optionC: "We may start flying",
          correctAnswer: "We may fall sick badly",
        },
        {
          question: "What is suggested to save water in the text?",
          optionA: "Leave taps running continuously",
          optionB: "Use a shower instead of a bucket for a bath",
          optionC: "Never leave taps running and use a bucket for a bath",
          correctAnswer: "Never leave taps running and use a bucket for a bath",
        },
        {
          question:
            "According to the text, what is the primary reason for saving water?",
          optionA: "To make plants grow faster",
          optionB: "Because the Earth is covered with water",
          optionC: "Due to the scarcity of freshwater",
          correctAnswer: "Due to the scarcity of freshwater",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is NOT mentioned as a tip for saving water in the text?",
          optionA: "Using leftover water to water plants",
          optionB: "Leaving taps running",
          optionC: "Taking only as much water as needed",
          correctAnswer: "Leaving taps running",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What can be concluded about the importance of water from the text?",
          optionA: "Water is not essential for living things",
          optionB:
            "Water is crucial for various activities and should be used wisely",
          optionC: "Water has no impact on health",
          correctAnswer:
            "Water is crucial for various activities and should be used wisely",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "Water is essential for all living things to stay alive. Except for drinking, we need water for different activities such as: to cook food, to wash clothes, to take a bath, to clean utensils, to mop the floor, and to ____________ out fire.",
          options: ["Light", "Put", "Extinguish"],
          correctAnswer: "Put",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Sources of Water: Rain is the main source of water. It feeds most of the other sources of water such as: river, lake, stream, and ____________.",
          options: ["Mountain", "Ocean", "Pond"],
          correctAnswer: "Pond",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Some rainwater seeps under the ground and gets collected there. We get this water from different sources such as: well, tube well, and ____________.",
          options: ["Reservoir", "Fountain", "Hand pump"],
          correctAnswer: "Hand pump",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Clean and Pure Water: Drinking water should be clean and pure. If we drink dirty water, we may fall sick badly. Boiled and filtered water is safe for ____________.",
          options: ["Cooking", "Bathing", "Drinking"],
          correctAnswer: "Drinking",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Save Water: Though most of the earth is covered with water, the amount of freshwater is very little. So, we should not waste it and use it wisely. We can follow some simple tips to save water: Never leave ____________ running.",
          options: ["Appliances", "Faucets", "Showers"],
          correctAnswer: "Faucets",
        },
        {
          question: "Use a bucket for a bath instead of a ____________.",
          options: ["Pool", "Lake", "Shower"],
          correctAnswer: "Shower",
        },
        {
          question: "Take only that much water you can ____________.",
          options: ["Carry", "Use", "Drink"],
          correctAnswer: "Drink",
        },
        {
          question: "Use leftover water to water the ____________.",
          options: ["Lawn", "Plants", "Trees"],
          correctAnswer: "Plants",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Rainwater seeping under the ground gets collected in a ____________.",
          options: ["Cave", "Well", "Tunnel"],
          correctAnswer: "Well",
        },
        {
          question: "If we drink dirty water, we may fall sick ____________.",
          options: ["Quickly", "Severely", "Mildly"],
          correctAnswer: "Severely",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "A tailor is responsible for stitching our clothes.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "A milkman sells us milk.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "A carpenter can make furniture.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "A cobbler can mend our shoes.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "A barber cuts our hair.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "A policeman protects us from thieves and robbers.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "A postman delivers us letters.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "A doctor can treat us when we fall ill.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "A watchman guards our houses at night.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "A shopkeeper sells us many things and services.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
